http://www.dieselstation.com/privacy.html

Download Our App
HomeBrowseCar PicturesLatest Car PicturesBrowse By Car ManufacturerA - CABT SportslineAcuraAlfa RomeoAMGApteraAscariAston MartinAudiBentleyBMWBrabusBrecklandBreitlingBugattiBuickCadillacCaparoCaterhamChevroletChevronChryslerCitroenD - FDaciaDaewooDaimlerDatsunDC DesignDelahayeDevon MotorsportsDodgeDonkervoortEdisonEternitiExagonFerrariFiatFiskerFM AutoFordG - LGemballaGMCGTA MotorsGumpertHoldenHondaHummerHyundaiIconaIFR AutomotiveInfinitiItalDesignIvecoJaguarJeepKiaKoenigseggKTMLamborghiniLanciaLand RoverLexusLincolnLotusLuxgenM - RMaseratiMaybachMazdaMcLarenMercedesMercuryMGMINIMitsubishiMorganMotorcyclesNice CarNissanNobleOpelOullimPaganiPanozPeugeotPhotographersPininfarinaPontiacPorscheProtonProtoscarQorosRacer X DesignRallyRenaultRevaRinspeedRolls RoyceS - ZSaabSaleenSaturnScionBike PicturesLatest Bike PicturesBrowse By Bike ManufacturerBMW PicturesBultaco PicturesDucati PicturesHonda PicturesKawasaki PicturesKTM PicturesMission Motors PicturesPeugeot PicturesSuzuki PicturesYamaha PicturesUser GalleriesGalleriesForumsContact UsFeedback
Login
Sign In
Register
Lost Password?
Quick Search :
ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPRSTUVWZ
Manufacturers
ABT SportslineAcuraAlfa RomeoAMGApteraAscariAston MartinAudiBentleyBMWBrabusBrecklandBreitlingBugattiBuickCadillacCaparoCaterhamChevroletChevronChryslerCitroenDaciaDaewooDaimlerDatsunDC DesignDelahayeDevon MotorsportsDodgeDonkervoortEdisonEternitiExagonFerrariFiatFiskerFM AutoFordGemballaGMCGTA MotorsGumpertHoldenHondaHummerHyundaiIconaIFR AutomotiveInfinitiItalDesignIvecoJaguarJeepKiaKoenigseggKTMLamborghiniLanciaLand RoverLexusLincolnLotusLuxgenMaseratiMaybachMazdaMcLarenMercedesMercuryMGMINIMitsubishiMorganMotorcyclesNice CarNissanNobleOpelOullimPaganiPanozPeugeotPhotographersPininfarinaPontiacPorscheProtonProtoscarQorosRacer X DesignRallyRenaultRevaRinspeedRolls RoyceSaabSaleenSaturnScion Tuners
AC SchnitzerAlpinaArashArdenART TuningBF PerformanceBrabusCarlssonCarrozzeria Touring SuperleggaraCobraDMCEdagEdo CompetitionEndoraFahrmitgasG-PowerGalpin Auto SportsGeigerCars.deHamannHartgeHS MotorsportHulmeJE DesignKelleners SportKW AutomotiveLOMA-PerformanceLSDLummaLupiniPowerMAE DesignManhart RacingMansoryMTMn2a MotorsNovitec RossoPiecha DesignPrior DesignProject KahnRace DesignRDSportReiter EngineeringRoockSpeedFactoryStarTechSteinmetzSuperformanceTechArtUnique SportCarsWheelsandmoreZagato Bikes
BMWBultacoDucatiHondaKawasakiKTMMission MotorsPeugeotSuzukiYamaha
Privacy
Updates > Site Updates
Privacy Policy
By using dieselstation.com, you agree to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this policy. If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our web site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we are going to use users' information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
We care seriously about protecting your privacy. Please send us any questions and/or comments you may have.
Summary
We will never spam you or give your personal information to anyone.
You can always request to remove your information from our servers and databases.
What information do we collect?
Personal: Name, email addresses, and password All passwords are stored on our server in encrypted form - even we can not tell what they are! If you lose your password, you request us to send a secret URL to your email address, using which you can reset your password. Usage: Number of logins, last login, activity and error logs This data helps us monitor dieselstation's health, interest and diagnose errors and slowness issues when they crop up.
How we treat your information?
We will never spam you. We will never disclose your personal information without your permission. We will never sell, rent or share your personal information with a 3rd party, especially your email addresses and phone numbers, without your express permission, unless required by law. Never ever!
We will only access your personal information when:
You specifically request us to do so (e.g. you are having technical difficulties).
It is required by law.
It is necessary to maintain our system.
Public Forums Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online for example on forums, on profile, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.
Cookies and log files
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Users must enable cookies to use our site. dieselstation.com sends a "cookie" to your computer that contains an identification number that is unique to you and the computer you are using. We use this cookie to provide you with a continuous experience, and for us to record how our service is being used.
As is done with most web sites, we log each visit to each web page. A log entry can contain information typically found in the "header" of your web browser's request such as the browser type you used, your Internet Protocol address, and the date and time of day. We may also log your cookie's identification number and the URL of the last site you visited. This log information is important for security, audit, quality improvement, as well as for monitoring the health of our service.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Third-party Advertising
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
Links
From time to time this web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, dieselstation, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the terms of use and privacy statements of each and every web site they visit. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Contacting the Web Site Admin
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please email us at .
Last Updated on April 14, 2010.
Request Car Quote
Views: 47647[Source: DieselStation]
Tags :
privacy
Hide Press Release
Privacy
Comments:
Latest Wallpapers
Following is the list of recent pictures updates on our site.
Morgan EV3 2017Morgan 4-4 80th Anniversary 2016Mercedes-Benz C63 AMG Coupe 2017Fiat Fullback Concept 2016
Car Pictures
Bike Pictures
DieselStation Social
Cars You May LikeFord GTFord Mustang Giugiaro ConceptAudi R8 Exclusive Selection Editions 2012Land Rover Range Rover 20132011 Hyundai ix35Mitsubishi Lancer (2008)Hyundai Tucson 2013
